{
  "Subjects": [
    {
      "Name": "ps",
      "Questions": [
        {
          "question": "Otazka 1",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "0"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 2",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 3",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 4",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 5",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "0"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "Name": "it",
      "Questions": [
        {
          "question": "Otazka 1it",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "0"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 2it",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 3it",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "2"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 4it",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "1"
        },
        {
          "question": "Otazka 5it",
          "options": [ "1", "2", "3" ],
          "answer": "0"
        }
      ]
    }

  ]
}